<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MyFilm</string>
    <string name="jungle">Jungle Cruise is a 2021 American fantasy adventure film directed by Jaume Collet-Serra from a screenplay written by Glenn Ficarra, John Requa, and Michael Green. It is based on Walt Disney\'s eponymous theme park attraction</string>
    <string name="deskripsi">Description</string>
    <string name="watch">Download Free Here</string>
    <string name="contentext">Jungle Cruise is a 2021 American fantasy adventure film directed by Jaume Collet-Serra from a screenplay written by Glenn Ficarra, John Requa, and Michael Green. It is based on Walt Disney\'s eponymous theme park attraction</string>
    <string name="contentext1">Venom is a 2018 American superhero film featuring the Marvel Comics character of the same name, produced by Columbia Pictures in association with Marvel[5] and Tencent Pictures. Distributed by Sony Pictures Releasing</string>
    <string name="contentext2">Free Guy is a 2021 American action-comedy film directed and produced by Shawn Levy from a screenplay by Matt Lieberman and Zak Penn, and a story by Lieberman.</string>
    <string name="contentext3"><![CDATA[Fast & Furious 9: The Fast Saga adalah film aksi Amerika tahun 2021 yang disutradarai oleh Justin Lin dan ditulis oleh Chris Morgan dan Daniel Casey. Sekuel dari film tahun 2017 The Fate of the Furious, itu akan menjadi angsuran kesepuluh dalam franchise Fast and the Furious dan film kesembilan di seri utama]]></string>
    <string name="contentext4">Turning Red is a 2022 American computer-animated fantasy comedy film produced by Pixar Animation Studios and distributed by Walt Disney Studios Motion Pictures. It was directed by Domee Shi in her feature directorial debut, written by Shi and Julia Cho, and produced by Lindsey Collins</string>
    <string name="contentext5">Ice Age is an American media franchise centering on a group of mammals surviving the Paleolithic ice age. It consists of computer-animated films, short films, TV specials and a series of video games. The first five films were produced by Blue Sky Studios</string>
    <string name="contentext6">Ice Age: The Meltdown atau Ice Age 2: The Meltdown adalah sebuah film animasi CGI tahun 2006 dan merupakan sekuel dari film Ice Age produksi tahun 2002. Film ini dibuat oleh Blue Sky Studios dan dirilis oleh 20th Century Fox pada 31 Maret 2006</string>
    <string name="contentext7">Lightyear is a 2022 American computer-animated science fiction action-adventure film produced by Pixar Animation Studios and distributed by Walt Disney Studios Motion Pictures. The film is a spin-off of the Toy Story film series, serving as an alternate or ideal origin story for the character Buzz Lightyear</string>
    <string name="contentext8">As a first grader, Mike Wazowski begins to dream of becoming a Scarer - a monster who enters the human world at night to scare children and harvest their screams for energy to power the city of Monstropolis. Eleven years later, Mike enrolls in the Scaring program at Monsters University (MU) and meets classmate James P. \"Sulley\" Sullivan. Abigail Hardscrabble, dean of MU, warns students that anyone who does not pass a final exam at the end of the first semester will have to leave the Scaring program.</string>
    <string name="contentext9">The Conjuring is a 2013 American supernatural horror film directed by James Wan and written by Chad Hayes and Carey W. Hayes. It is the inaugural film in the Conjuring Universe franchise.[</string>
    <string name="contentext10">KKN di Desa Penari adalah film horor Indonesia tahun 2022 yang disutradarai oleh Awi Suryadi berdasarkan cerita viral berjudul sama karya SimpleMan. Film produksi MD Pictures serta Pichouse Films ini dibintangi oleh Tissa Biani, Adinda Thomas, dan Achmad Megantara.</string>
    <string name="contentext11">Scream is an American horror slasher franchise that includes five films, a television series, merchandise, and games. The series has grossed over $740 million in worldwide box-office receipts.</string>
    <string name="contentext12">Satan\'s Slaves (Indonesian: Pengabdi Setan) is a 2017 Indonesian gothic horror film written and directed by Joko Anwar. It is a loose remake-prequel to the 1980 film of the same name directed by Sisworo Gautama Putra based on a story by Subagio S.</string>
    <string name="contentext13">After a post-graduation road trip, Elle still hasn\'t decided between going to Berkeley or Harvard – although Noah is already looking for an off-campus apartment for them. When Noah and Lee\'s parents announce they\'re selling the beach house where they all spent their childhoods, Elle, Noah, Lee, and Lee\'s girlfriend, Rachel, spend the summer there to help prepare for the sale.</string>
    <string name="contentext14">Natalie Bauer is a Los Angeles-based dating column writer who documents her disastrous dates she meets via a dating app. After deciding to expand the app\'s search radius, Natalie matches with a man named Josh Lin and forms a strong connection to him through many long phone calls. She decides to travel to his hometown in Lake Placid, New York to surprise him for Christmas, promising her boss this will be the end to her dating disasters. However, she soon discovers that she has been catfished by Josh, who used another man\'s pictures</string>
    <string name="contentext15">Iqbal (Angga Yunanda) seperti kupu-kupu Mariposa bagi Acha (Adhisty Zara). Tiap kali didekati ia selalu menghindar. Acha bertekad ingin mendapatkan hati Iqbal, seorang cowok cakep, pintar dan dikenal berhati dingin. Ternyata sikap dingin Iqbal itu tuntutan dari sang ayah yang menginginkannya menang dalam olimpiade sains</string>
    <string name="contentext16">Negeri Van Oranje adalah film drama petualangan Indonesia yang dirilis pada 23 Desember 2015. Film ini diadaptasi dari sebuah novel dengan judul yang sama karya Wahyuningrat. Film ini menjalani pengambilan gambar di Belanda, Ceko, dan Indonesia.</string>
</resources>